see him mr. Foyle we actually you know
we're going to be inducted Sam Tim milk
and he has people here from Rancho
Michigan and his son for sylvania many
people one of the items of insulting the
very first Albert person of Korean
heritage into Cleveland international
holiday and resin leaders as well as
members of the Korean creating that one
is information unit us but Sam said no
there's no better person than not me
there's no better person to juvie I know
that my son of tea it was very wet it's
always this whole to go after some
dynamic speaker so you know I I wanted
to kind of reflect on the things that my
father's come through the years and the
first thing I could think of is I'm in
Cleveland Ohio I just want to make sure
that is my ground here was but no one
threw anything at me now but thank you
very much and I hope in bridgend tonight
and if I follow along and stumble a
little bit because we're honoring my dad
so this fall beeping so good evening
Debbie attention my name is Keith him I
have the arch night and jumping my
father some him into the Cleveland
international all things so they know
about an American named Sam count by the
way I am honored tonight for being able
to speak about my father can be half of
the korean-american community in
cleveland in northeast ohio wealth my
family when I think of the Hall of Fame
I think of great for Kira and this is
for you Cleveland like Jim Brown Bob
Feller or Roberto Alomar but what does
it mean to be a Hall of Famer for the
international community here in
Cleveland well it means you're honoring
your heritage your culture while
promoting its others for my dad and
fulfill this late in his life and he
visited on back so let me tell you about
few of those
my dad became president of the korean
american association of north northeast
ohio he worked with the South Korean
government to organize and run a
homeless veteran event by giving away
jacket point is the 12 a warm meal he
also sponsored and organized a
commemorative medal ceremony for Korean
War veterans throughout Ohio you see my
dad in an immigrant and he didn't speak
the language very well it is how
resources but he has perseverance so
believe in himself the belief in its
family and most importantly the guiding
can about my dad did not take up these
and others was beginning he was
reluctant he was in a small town but he
had braids all for his community which
cushioned be involved today recognized
for all goodie it works but I must
remind everyone Hall of Famers aren't
instantly created there they have innate
ability to be driven distraction the
best become better calm that exemplifies
my father
oui oui
[Applause]
I have a problem gasping but I see
people thank you everyone and thank you
also shut up marginal rate and HK mark
it also Nebraska there was about okay
well if I stick it in her people were
afraid I did know what we do nothing
will come here to try instead we're here
you have learned one lesson for you haha
I say hello how are you so he is real I
knew how they say it as everyone i know
i'm your papi oh thank god
[Applause]